Actually, every year I get an invitation for Independence Day from my old school.
But
this time it has crossed all limits.  The children have
sent such a beautiful card.  But it is my headache due to which
I could not sleep the whole night
and at 5:00 in the morning someone rang the bell.   As soon as I
opened the door, I saw Maya
standing with a sword.  She says get it ready quickly.
Today I have to go as Rani Lakshmibai.   Yes
friends, I am that sister who
prepares all the children in the neighborhood.
Now, I am not an expert in changing the colour and appearance
but I can do some minor
paint and putty work.  For which, I
applied the shadows on my eyes using my phone and
then got my skin prepped by applying toner.
Hey, when will this be useful?  Let me show you my wealth of ₹1 ₹200.
After that,
apply the moisturizer which is mixed free in this product.
Stroop cream for a little sunscreen glow.  Take Plaster Complete.  Now
we will apply putty from face to neck.   We will
also paint our cheeks a little and apply bright red
lipstick.  Then I started doing my eye
makeup properly.  I have
n't even washed my face but today I am going to make his face
shine completely.  Nice eyeliner.
Applying eye shadow and we poor people do
n't have a big bindi.  Therefore, the
trick of Jiyamati has been applied to a small bindi and stuck on the forehead
and the hairstyle is going to be very simple
because a crown will come on top of it.
Now you guys quickly tell me
how many marks out of 10 will you give to this Mistri Giri of mine.  Till then
aunty is making me wear the saree
and look at my sister Golu, she is going to go
in Kumaoni look today.  But poor bald Lakha
boys are like this, brother.  Come on
then, let's all eat Bundi Laddus.
Celebrate Independence Day.  Hearty greetings to everyone,
Radhe-Radhe.